## **Clinton Garwood**

## Personal Statement

I am a passionate, proactive, and goal-driven leader looking for an entry-level position in a company where I can combine my four-year university education with over 5 years of experience in Sales and Customer Service to promote company growth.

### **Education**

 Stony Brook University Bachelor of Arts August 2011 / December 2015

**Major:** Cinema and Cultural Studies

Minor: Digital Arts, Creative Writing, Africana Studies

Organizations and Awards

<u>Caribbean Students Organization:</u> Vice President, Cultural Officer, Promotional Officer, Creative Director/Media Representative, Freshman Representative.

**Educational Opportunities Program:** Outstanding Writers Award (2011)





### **Work Experience**

- WHARTON EXTERMINATING SERVICES | OPERATIONS/MARKETING | QUEENS, NEW YORK | NOVEMBER 2016- CURRENT |
  - Manage the operation and administration of company finances, resources, and employees.
  - Organized sales strategies focused on serving residential pest control market.
  - Acquired and retained clientele through targeted PPC marketing and high-level customer service.
  - Built company trust and credibility by educating clients and potential clients on products, services, and personal practices for effective pest control.

#### **Additional Skills & Traits**

Communication - Customer Service – Planning – Networking - Goal Setting & Meeting - Customer Retention - Generating Sales - Product Knowledge - Detail Oriented - Punctual - Team Player - Problem Solving - Maximize Business Opportunities

#### SELF-EMPLOYED | RIDE-SHARE | NEW YORK, NY | FEBRUARY 2016- CURRENT |

- Maintained a steady 4.9-5.0 driver rating through effective customer service and friendly conversation.
- Increased tip frequency by providing additional amenities such as film, libation, and personal hygiene products.
- Scouted areas/hours of highest lead frequency to maximize earnings

# GAP INC. | SALES ASSOCIATE/DENIM SPECIALIST | NEW YORK, NY | MAY 2011- DECEMBER 2014 |

- Interface with customers to identify purchasing needs and direct them to appropriate Gap departments; recommended additional products or cost-effective alternatives to enhance service and satisfaction.
- Champion promotional items to increase sales revenues and actualize consultative sales techniques to achieve set goals.
- Educated customers on available product options to meet and exceed customer service experience.
- Investigated and resolved customer complaints or issues to strengthen store reputation and grow customer retention.

## STONY BROOK STUDENTS ORG. | VICE PRESIDENT / MEDIA REP. | LONG ISLAND, NEW YORK | SEPTEMBER 2011- DECEMBER 2015 |

- Regularly negotiated with the student government for \$20,000 in yearly funding for club events and community service initiatives.
- Organized and hosted weekly general body meetings of current event topics.
- Successfully attracted over 100 students weekly through effective physical and social media marketing.





+1 (914) 215-3322



ClintonGarwood@Gmail.com